caida.org 2019-06-09

# CAIDA Website Privacy Policy

### What information do we collect?

When registering on our site or filling out a form, e.g., to sign up for a mailing list or request data, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number or institutional affiliation. You may, however, visit our site anonymously. 

### What do we use your information for?

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways: 

  * To process dataset requests 

Your information will not be transferred to any other organization without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the information product or service requested and complying with internal sponsor requirements and scientific research transparency objectives. 

  * To send periodic emails 

The email address you provide will only be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your request/inquiry. 

Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, If you wish to be removed from receiving future emails please indicate so in a message to data-info@caida.org. CAIDA retains contact information related to dataset registration in case CAIDA needs to inform you of a change in the Acceptable Use Policy or detected measurement errors in the data. 

### How do we protect your information?

All supplied personal information is maintained securely and accessible only by authorized users, and maintained on file only as long as necessary to fulfill internal sponsor requirements and scientific research transparency objectives. 

### Do we use cookies?

Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. We use cookies to compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can improve our web site experience and tools. 

### Do we disclose any information to outside parties?

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information without your consent, except to research sponsors who enable our data stewardship, and trusted research partners who assist us in pursuing legitimate research. For registered dataset users, CAIDA has obtained consent to make public or otherwise disclose those users' names, their affiliated institutions, the name(s) of the dataset(s) that CAIDA has made available to them, and a brief description of the type of research being undertaken. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. 

### Online Privacy Policy Only

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline. 

### Acceptable Use Policies

Please also visit our Acceptable Use Policies section establishing the access obligations, use and disclosure restrictions, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing CAIDA data sets at <http://www.caida.org/data/collection/aup/>. 

### Your Consent

By using our site, you consent to our web site privacy policy. 

### Changes to our Privacy Policy

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, and/or update the Privacy Policy modification date below. 

This policy was last modified on November 24, 2011. 

### Contacting Us

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below. 

> Center for Applied Internet Data Analysis  
>  University of California San Diego  
>  9500 Gilman Dr., MC0505  
>  La Jolla, California 92093  
>  United States  
>  data-info@caida.org  
>  www.caida.org
